Here we go, Aust TV!
I'm Haruka Yamashita from Aichi Prefecture.
And I'm Momo Wakabayashi.
Last year, a mysterious TV station, Oosu TV, suddenly appeared.
Haruharu, a new announcer, and Momo-chan, an influencer, explore the trends and beauty of Osu, the cultural center of Nagoya.
This time, these young comedians who will lead the next generation also came to visit us.
Hello, please!
Stretchies, please!
Please, please, please, please, please.
Please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please!
A Nagoya-only unit organized by K-pro, a comedy live show organizer.
Stretchies from Nagokpachi will join us again this time!
They are expected to be the next breakout comedian with their authentic comic storytelling style!
It's a pleasure to see Haruharu again, who is expected to be the next breakout comedian with Haruharu as his weapon of choice.
Happy to see Haruharu again!
Haruharu!
What do you mean?
Did you forget?
Okay, bye.
There's something I didn't get a chance to tell you.
I was wondering if you could show me something.
Here?
I'd like to see it.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
I don't get a lot of this stuff.
Shall we do some of this?
Are you sure?
I'm a comic.
What do you mean?
Short comedy.
I'll do a short one.
Thank you very much.
Hi, I'm Srecki.
I've come up with an original psych test. Imagine this.
You're the best rock musician in Japan... and you hold a concert... and the number of people in the audience is...
I see... so the number of people is connected to the answer... I see... so you're saying that this number of people is connected to the answer.
Did you guess? I did.
That number is the number of children you will have in the future.
How's that possible?
You're right.
Wait, wait!
I imagined 50,000, but are you sure?
50,000?
That's right.
I'm two.
I don't know why you're asking me that.
Thank you very much.
How many did you imagine, by the way... 600, 600.
How many did you imagine, by the way?
Six hundred.
That's great.
I'll lift you up.
Thank you very much.
This time, I'd like to report on the four of us.
Let's do a thorough report.
Let's go!
From the hottest spots
From the hottest spots to the most exquisite sweets!
In this second installment of our gourmet theme, we're going to come up with a new Nagoya cuisine that's sure to be a hit in the future!
And those who came to help us with the filming are...
Selina and Noah!
They won the right to appear on the show by auditioning for the live-streaming service Showroom.
They won the right to appear on the show through an audition for the live-streaming service Showroom.
By the way, I, Autumn Scent, who is in charge of narration
I, Autumn Scent, who narrates the show, was also selected through an audition.
Please check out our live-streaming showroom!
We're all looking for a good time in Aus!
I'm sure you'll want to visit, too!
Nagoya's cultural center
With the theme of "Aust.
Aus TV, the place to seek out the best of Aus.
First of all First up.
Haruharu vs Momo-chan
New Nagoya rice making showdown!
Decorate the pancakes shown here.
We're going to make a new Nagoya food that's going to be a hot topic in the future.
We're going to ask you two to make a new Nagoya food that will be a hit in the future.
It's called a cooking showdown.
A decoration showdown.
That's right.
But it's also important to be a good cook and a good decorator, so...
arrangement of dishes.
I'll do my best.
It's a showdown, so the loser gets a buzz game.
Here's what we've prepared to invent the new Nagoya food!
We've prepared a variety of Nagoya specialties.
Please make pancakes that will create a buzz!
Let's get started!
There are all kinds of things.
Lots of pipes and stuff.
Do you usually cook?
I don't.
Haruharu is a beginner cook.
What's the first thing you picked up?
It's tough.
Haruharu might pull a wing.
Haruharu.
Haruharu, that doesn't sound good, does it?
Don't tell me you don't want the wings on the whip, huh? Haruharu that doesn't look good, does it? Ohhhh, I'm not gonna read too much into it.
Don't tell me
Chicken wings on whip
Haruharu seems to have it all figured out.
Very nice.
Are you serious?
Yes, I am.
Really?
A little.
But what is it now?
Don't you get it? Don't you get it?
It's a killer whale.
What's a "box"?
What's a hoko?
The orca and the hoko on top of the love john.
Orca and hoko?
The answer was a little weird, but Haruharu seemed to be doing well.
What about Momochan, on the other hand?
Does Momochan cook? Once upon a time...
So cold!
Momochan is cold when she cooks.
What was that? You used to?
What?
I made a mistake.
Really?
I'm not talking to you.
He's talking on his own. You don't have to listen to him.
I heard he used to do this.
Apparently, they're this cute...
I can't believe they're decorating.
They're decorating.
It's kind of creepy.
It's a nice sight, isn't it?
And here...
Fukushima-san has a request for Haruharu and Momo-chan.
Mr. Fukushima has a favor to ask of Haruha and Momo-chan.
When I come home after a long day at work...
When I come home after a hard day's work
Can I have a few words of encouragement?
Is that self-serving?
No, no, no. I'm just trying to make it fun for the audience.
Momochan's cooking right now.
Is that self-serving?
I've never heard that before on TV.
It's not personal.
Then, Momochan, what would you like to say to me when I come home from work and I'm tired?
What name would you like to be called?
My first name is Toshiki, so Toshiki. My first name is Toshiki, so I'm Toshiki.
First of all, here's Momochan's moe line.
Welcome back, Toshiki!
Welcome back, Toshiki.
Shall we move to a bigger place?
No, thanks.
How come you've got a stable income?
I decline.
Let's move on to the next big-ticket item.
Then stop it!
I'll think of something.
That's so rude.
Welcome back, Toshikiku.
Good work today.
Everyone gave him a big thumbs up!
Haruharu's moe line will be in the second half of the show.
Next up.
I'd like to go wandering around the offs from here on that moe line will follow in the second half of the program
From here, we'd like to take a stroll around Oost.
Aust is all about sweets, right?
That's right.
There are all kinds of sweets here.
I heard there's a store coming soon.
What is it?
It's this way.
What is it? This way!
Sweet potato's.
Sweet potato stuff
Sweet potato's
Sweet potato no mono no mono noo!
Suddenly my Japanese is not good enough!
Imomi-san
The four of us came to
A store that is popular for its sweet treats using sweet potatoes
Imomi Osten
Store Imomi Osten Store Imomi-Osutenshop
It's a store. Cute.
It's cute!
Nice to meet you!
The sweets are delicious!
It's true.
Which one is it?
Looks delicious.
They're so cute!
They all look delicious!
But this one says "most recommended".
The name of the store is the same as the name of the store.
I'm curious!
The fact that they put their name on it means they're really into it.
Then let's have this umomi.
I'll have one, please.
Thank you very much.
It looks so delicious!
It's so shiny, so delicious, so shiny...
Looks so delicious!
I can't wait to eat it!
I can't wait to eat it.
First of all, let's take a picture with my phone!
Smile!
I'm scared.
They say I'm scary.
They're saying you're scary.
Stick out your tongue a little.
Uncle Dan, you don't have to do it so fast... they say I'm scared.
You don't have to do it either, Haruharu.
What a sequence of events!
It's so good!
It's really good, but...
I don't feel like doing too much har-har-har
In that case
The subject is in the middle here.
the top and bottom will be extended. The top and bottom will stretch.
It's better to keep them in the middle as much as possible.
So if you take a full body, if the feet are on the bottom, the feet will grow longer.
So if you take a full body, if the legs are on the bottom, the legs will stretch properly.
The top and bottom will stretch.
That's why we open the top and put the feet on the bottom.
That's a popular influencer.
Taking his advice, I tried again.
I'm going to eat it.
Let's try to eat it.
Are you okay?
It's going really well!
The price is very instagrammable!
I got the doctor's seal of approval!
It's pretty good.
How'd you learn that?
Do you have an Instagrammer girlfriend? You're a good teacher! How did you learn that? Do you have an Instagrammer girlfriend?
The teacher is good.
It was cloudy this time.
Cloudy is the best time to show your face.
That's right.
Too much sunlight.
The light jumps around a little bit.
If you just look at your face, it leaks.
so I think the weather was on my side.
I guess the weather was a good thing.
That's great.
I've never heard of it before.
I've been eating them on Instagram.
Now that we've taken some good pictures, it's time for the eagerly awaited tasting!
I'm going to try it.
You're going to do a report on the food?
May I?
Haruharu, have a good day!
I'll go ahead and try it first.
It's so moist! I can already tell! Bon appétit.
So cute!
Delicious! Delicious!
It's pretty painful.
- Speak up! Don't say it!
- Don't say it! It's delicious!
- That's what I thought afterwards.
I know, I know.
This sponge really disappears in an instant.
The sweet potato mont blanc on top!
Creamy
It's insanely delicious!
It's a match made in heaven!
It's so good!
Delicious, isn't it?
It's amazing!
The sponge disappears in an instant and it's like Mont Blanc, it's so good! The sponge disappears in an instant.
The part that looks like Mont Blanc is so good!
Delicious, isn't it?
It's so fluffy!
It looks good and it's delicious!
The sponge melts in an instant.
Imomi
If you're interested, you can check it out in Aust... where we're headed right now.
Not Haruharu?
Haruharu is asking me?
There are so many places to store.
I want to go in all of them.
You're curious about all of them, aren't you?
What is this place?
C-Plus.
Isn't it great?
Capsule Toys
Capsule toy store
There are so many capsule toys!
Oh my God!
There are so many!
They're amazing!
Oh my God, they're so cute! Oh my God, it's so cute!
The four of us discovered a capsule toy specialty store
C-pla Nagoya Otsu Store
One of the largest capsule toy stores in the Tokai area with 1,376 capsule toys!
In reference to Nagoya's morning culture, the store's atmosphere is based on the theme of a coffee shop.
The coffee shop-themed atmosphere is one of the attractions of the store.
There are so many!
Can you spin these?
Ta-da!
What?
Oh, it's heavy.
It's so heavy! It's so heavy! It's so cute!
Even the one Haruhara prepared for me, please. No, it's not.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no...
I hope it's all budget, no budget... because how could it be?
So, Momochan, you just go ahead and turn in whatever catches your fancy, and we'll see what we can come up with.
What's the point?
What's Momochan's favorite thing?
Is this going to be like a prize show?
Keep looking!
I'm so glad.
There are so many, it's hard to choose.
What about the capsule chosen by a popular influencer?
I saw a lot of capsules chosen by popular influencers, but I want the punch at the entrance.
I want the one that says "recommend staff" I want the one that says "punch" I hope it's cute I've got a Momo-chan so I'll give it a shot
I'll go for it!
What do you think?
I love it!
I wonder...
What do you think?
Neil, go full throttle.
Here we go.
I don't know.
It's a swimming pool.
It's a pool.
Surfing.
Surfing! Surfing
You did it!
You did the pool pool pool pool! We did the pool pool pool pool! Pool! Pool! Pool!
Yeah!
You did it!
You can swim!
Yeah. - Yeah.
Come on! Let's get back on track!
What the hell?
What?
Hmm?
Surfing.
From the pool.
That's my favorite.
I'd like to get a little guess at it.
Next time.
What do you say?
Pool?
I like pool too much.
I'm surprised I don't hit more than I should.
You've been to too many night pools.
One more time.
I'm gonna get so sunburned.
Please, next time.
You're right.
Jankan Frozen!
Yay!
That's great!
It's like this. It's like this.
It's all around the water.
So, what do you want to do, Haruharu?
Me?
Let's see what Haruharu has in store for us.
I just found something I want to do.
Haruharu.
Okay?
You can do it as many times as you want.
You sure?
Har-har-har, you can do it as many times as you want.
What is this?
It's a balloon.
It's cute.
Shoulder pouch.
I've missed these.
Which one do you want?
The toy box, too.
This one?
What?
Not the whistle lovelies?
Definitely the whistle lovelies!
What's that?
Type B is better.
I'm sure this big one is better.
I'll make it smell like a Type B.
It's so good!
Four hundred yen.
That's right. It's already 300 yen again.
Totally fine.
Kind of.
You can spend as much as you want, even 500 yen. Totally fine. Even 500 yen.
Not at all.
You can spend even this.
A little.
Then, I'd like to put it in.
Okay.
Well, do you think it'll come out? Oh, do you think he'll show up?
I hope you'll come to Eframel.
I have a feeling.
Oh, oh, I think it's coming.
It's here.
Yes, it did.
No, when it came out.
That's amazing.
It's not this sensitive when it comes out.
But now...
What is it?
Are you sure it's not Type B? Are you sure it's not Type B? Wait a minute. I don't know what's wrong with you, but you're really not a Type B.
Wait a minute.
It's not a Type B.
It's seriously not a Type B.
Type B.
It's a Type B.
Oh, my God.
That's a hit.
I didn't expect it to be a one-shot deal!
The power of Haruharu!
I want you to listen to the flute Ramune!
I wonder if the flute Ramune will come out.
I'm not going to get it a second time...
I wonder if something will come out
What do you think it'll be?
Type B, I think.
There it goes.
What's going on?
I don't think so.
I don't know.
It's amazing!
It's too much!
Here it is.
That's great!
I knew it! I knew it!
A woman who doesn't cost a fortune.
I'd appreciate it if we went on a date.
I'd like to send you the uncut version of this.
I really only turned it twice.
You hit the pool twice earlier.
I didn't win a lot of pools.
It's spring.
Oh, my God.
That's cute, even for a FNMM, but yeah, it's cute.
I'm glad you and the staff were able to help us out with the budget.
I'm just patting myself on the back.
Thank you very much.
Osu is lined with many other attractive stores!
Selina and Noah will introduce you to a popular Korean sweet, Oniwassan!
Serina and Noah are going to introduce you to the hottest sweet oniwassan in Korea!
What kind of sweets are they?
Thank you very much.
Thank you very much!
So cute!
It's so cute!
It's shaped like a rice ball.
Looks delicious.
You've never had it?
No, I haven't.
Like this?
Take a pretty picture. Make it pretty.
That's good, that's good.
Take a pretty picture.
I don't know.
Make it more, make it more...
Make me look good.
It's a suit.
You're going all out.
I'm so excited.
Take it. Open your eyes.
It's not like that. It's a little not like that.
Maybe it's that kind of thing.
It doesn't look good.
Why not?
We don't look good. We don't look good.
We don't look good... we don't look good... we don't look good... we don't look good...
We don't look good.
Let's ask.
Can you take a picture for me?
Can you take a pretty picture for me?
I couldn't do it myself.
Now that we have two models, I'll be able to use the skills I've learned so far.
It's like you're looking at them.
It's really good.
It's so dynamic.
Well, I don't think they get along.
Well, I don't think they're good friends, but... well, I don't think they're good friends, but...
They're good friends
Unusual tskkis
Unusual tsk tsk.
Oath TV's "tsk tsk.
Now, how does it taste?
The dough is really crispy, but the flavor is kneaded into the dough, so it's really delicious!
I'm sure it will be very popular in Japan in the future!
Looks delicious!
Delicious!
What's wrong?
What's wrong? What's wrong? Where are my cheeks?
Your cheeks are actually falling off!
After the commercial, here you go!
Haruharu's Moeserin-kun!
A must-see for all the fans!
Now, on to the big one!
I've just come home from work and I'm tired, and you've got something to say to me that makes me squeal!
Okay, here we go! Okay, I'll go now.
Click.
Welcome back, Toshikiku!
Thanks for your hard work today.
Let's share pancakes I made with lots of love.
I love them so much!
Wow!
Yum!
Including this.
I said it myself.
And this cutout.
Our faces are red.
Why are we all blushing?
What are you doing? Four of us.
Now it's time for the finale.
What will our new Nagoya food be?
Is the new Nagoya rice we've come up with really done?
It's done!
You did a great job!
It's wonderful!
First of all, Harumaru!
I made two Nagoya rice wings.
Wow, what an impact!
This is the company's first child, isn't it?
Very good!
I tried to express the blood of this Osu memory in letters
I put it on this pancake too!
It's not such a big deal.
I wrote Osu.
Because it's Osu TV, you wrote Osu.
It's full of love, isn't it?
It's my hometown, so I love Osu.
I'm a homesteader who makes custom cakes in Korea or something.
Don't forget that.
I'm scared.
I'm like Jobal's senior.
What did Stretchies choose? What did Stretch's choose?
Spring Spring
I like this one.
What? What?
It's definitely a contact!
But these were really cut lines.
Really?
To be honest, I thought Momochan would be the best, but...
But I still think it's too much in the direction of the president to be called "New Nagoya Meal".
I thought there was a little too much love for Nagoya.
Unfortunately, Momochan lost the game, so she had to be punished.
That's the worst!
Please share this one with us!
May I?
Yes, ma'am.
Who decorated with flowers?
I can't do this.
No, but it's pretty.
Decorated pretty.
Actually, these edible turtles
You can buy them at Ozu!
Momo, please write a food report!
I can not see Haruharu!
Turtles?
Haruharu already!
Wait!
I can not look directly at it
Haruharu, I'm not going to eat it, but it's like this
He said it's making him sick.
Please enjoy the food.
I'm at fault here.
It's great! I'm in a ghost-loving state.
Bon appétit.
Wow, that's great.
Hey, hey, hey, now.
I'll put on the tone.
Um...
It's the difference between Mom and Momo. It's the difference between Mom and Momo.
Hey, hey, hey, say it once and say something funny like this... Ahhh... You're so brave.
What?
The surprisingly sweet edible tamame.
You should look for them when you come to Ozu!
How did you two like it?
After all, we were able to take a stroll through the Ozu shopping district.
I was reminded once again that this is a place that is loved by a wide range of people.
I'm thinking of doing a little more work on the food in the future.
That's right.
I've decided.
Your comment about Haruharu is like sunshine.
I'm in a really blue mood.
It's taking everything I've got.
I'm eating bugs at the end.
It was amazing.
I hope that next time we'll have a comedian who doesn't have to go through the discovery process.
No discovery.
No?
No.
Not as Janko.
It's a close call.
Yes, sir.
I have one last announcement.
The photos we took today will be
We'll be updating them on the show's official Instagram and TikTok.
We will be updating them on our official Instagram and TikTok.
So please check it out!
See you next time!
Bye bye!
bye-bye!